my name is jim andrew I'm a program manager on the windows networking team.
Today I'll be talking about what is hot spot to dot au and how you can
connector windows ten devices to hot spot to networks?
Hot spot to...also known as past point
...next generation hotspots is based on I triple...is eight two dot eleven
new standard it brings many new improvements to how we currently discover and
connect to hot spot networks.
If you go to an airport or coffee shop you'll see many open hot spot networks you
cannot be sure which ones are owned by the right authorities and which ones are owned by malicious
users trying-to sniff on your internet activities
in contrast all hot spot to networks are security using w
...to enterprise you also don't have to scroll through multiple
networks anymore and figure out which one you may have credentials for windows
tent automatically discovers and connect to the right hot spot to
networks for you next up let's take a look at the connection process?
To connect to hot spot to network you first need to download a profile for
it the hot spot to profile schema is simply
an update to the existing windows profile schema it contains certain additional
fields unique to...by to networks.
Once you have downloaded a profile and your...range of valid hot spot to networks windows can
communicate with those networks and determine whether you have the credentials for them this
communication happens over a new protocol called access query network protocol
Once your devices validated that you have the right set of
credentials so go ahead and automatically connect you
to that network device can connect to that network using a
...card...password...certificate base credential.
You can use the profile provisioning api to download the hot spot to profile on a windows
...device to
provision profile you need to pass the api.
Valid provisioning xml
sign using an extended validation certificate the
signing is required to validate that the profile as being provision by the right
owners of the profile and no one else next up let's see in end-to-end demo
...provisioning...hot spot to profile and automatically connecting to hot spot to network.
To get started simply visit the hot spot to dot
...provisioning website in this case where using boeing those one.
Enter any credentials required and go ahead and download the profile.
Once the profile has been downloaded successfully please disconnect from the wi-fi network
...currently connected to you don't need to do this if you're not connected to any networks.
Once...range of...hot spot
two-dollar network you'll be connected automatically to it it's as simple as that.
If you read build and have received a...handout you can try out the demo yourself please
make sure you have the right windows ten build and the latest...installed you can find
that additional details about how...do the provisioning on the handout itself?
Hot spot to dot...works on all windows
ten devices with hot spot to capable hardware.
If you have a device running windows ten you can check if it supports
hot spot to buy running the following command and command prompt type in net sh w
land show wireless capabilities if the
...copy service information discovery element is supported
...all set I hope we had fun learning about hot spot to dot...and how windows
ten devices can connect to them please take a look at the given resources and
try connecting to hot spot to networks near you thank you for watching?